I'm scared. Scared to dig too deep into myself.
Hmm. Your work's not bad. It's alright, but... How do I put this? Readers want to see what
makes an artist tick. You gotta dig deep down into yourself. That's what art's all about.
You say you're 29 now? Yeah, our magazine might not be the best fit for you.
The 2006 World Cup in Germany is only 26 days away.
If only I'd done things different is a phrase that pops into my head every day.
I don't think about it too seriously though.
Just words. As soon as they come to mind.
They disappear.
I'm scared. Scared to dig too deep into myself.
Heading out on a delivery.
Okay. Drive safe.
I'm heading out on one too.
Kay, drive safe out there.
Poojinuma, keep your stomach away from that pizza, you hear?
Geez. Is that what kids are calling humor these days?
I will.
Fun fact. She says that to me every day. It's the only thing she says to me.
Far as I can tell, she's got zero feelings for me. She's so weird. Too weird, too young.
There it was. It happened again. Where is it? Something's not right. But what?
Hey! You in the truck! Pull over!
Yo! Stop the truck!
Wait!
Wait, that's Poojinuma. What's he doing?
Goddammit! I can't believe I'm doing this!
Why am I doing this?
Come on!
Oh my god!
You okay?
What am I looking at?
Oh. It's my life flashing before my eyes.
This is what happens when you get involved with other people's problems.
Oh well. If I'm dead, I'm dead. Who cares?
Huh?
You opened your eyes.
It's about time. You were out for two days.
Katagiri?
Hiya, Sleeping Beauty. So, do you know who you are and how you got here?
Satoru Fujinuma. I'm 29. I was chasing the truck and I got hit.
Awesome! The truck said it's a miracle you didn't get hurt more.
Do you want me to go call someone for you? Like a friend or girlfriend or something?
Uh-uh. There isn't anyone I want to bother telling.
Snip, snip.
I don't get it. That's supposed to be funny?
No, I'm just trying to cut through that thick cocoon you're in.
You come off like the type who doesn't open up or care about anyone.
The non-laughing type. But after the other day, I know better.
How so?
You saved that kid's life. I was right there and I saw the whole thing go down.
And you know that truck driver? Well, I heard he had a heart attack and died at the wheel.
I still don't get how you noticed that.
Lucky, I guess.
Yeah, well, the truck crashed into a warehouse and amazingly, you and the driver were the only casualties.
What about the damages?
I told our manager what happened and he says insurance will take care of the bike in the other car.
And then when you get better, come back to work.
That's good news.
Ha! I caught you smiling.
How come you work at the pizza place? It can't be for the money.
Wow. Now there's a personal question.
Oh, sorry, was it?
Mm-hmm. In fact, you're the first person to ever ask me that. I work there because I have a dream.
That's cool.
Don't you want to know what it is?
Well, aren't you worried that it jinxed it for you? Besides, if it didn't come true, people would think you're a loser.
Oh, I'm not worried about telling anyone. The more I talk about it, the better the chance it'll come true. That's what I think anyway.
Wait. Where have I heard that before?
You know what? I decided I'm not going to tell you about it after all.
What?
It's not like we're dating or anything like that.
I'm gonna let the nurse know you're awake and then I'm going home. See ya!
Man, she's weird.
I have a name for what happens to me.
Revival.
It never benefits me, but I play along with it anyway.
When it happens, I go back in time anywhere from one to five minutes.
And it always happens before something bad goes down.
It's like someone's forcing me to fix whatever's gone wrong, so I start looking for the one thing that seems, you know, off.
I've managed to stop a lot of tragedies, so far.
Most of the time, I fix whatever bad's supposed to happen and everything comes out okay.
But sometimes, like this time, things go bad for me.
For me.
Oh. Hey there, Satoru.
Hey, Mom.
I went to the hospital, but you were out cold. Sorry I didn't stay, but I got bored watching you sleep.
So, how's your head doing, kiddo?
It's fine.
Yeah, right. They told me you had a head-on with a car.
I'll be staying for a while.
Huh? What do you mean, you're staying?
What do you think I mean? I want to make sure my little guy's okay. A car hit you, for Christ's sakes.
You don't have to. I said I'm fine. Anyway, I only have one futon.
No worries. I can make do with the sleeping bag I found in the closet.
A hotel's better.
Nah, hotel's too expensive.
Oh, then I can pay you back for the hospital and...
So keep it and we'll call it my rent.
She's 52, but looks the same as when I was a kid. Same attitude, too.
Satoru, do I have to change trains to get to Ueno?
No, you don't.
Wait, you want to go sightseeing?
Well, I did come all the way from Hokkaido. Besides, if I had to look at your face all day, I'd get bored.
You haven't even been here a whole day yet, Mom.
Come on. Let's eat.
I took over your futon and TV. Sorry.
No, it's cool. This sucks. If I need to use the bathroom later, I'll have to tiptoe around her.
Hey, if you need to use the bathroom later, don't worry about tiptoeing around me. I'm gonna sleep like a log tonight.
Witch.
And now for our next story. Yesterday evening, we told you about a first grade girl from Saitama who went missing.
Well, I'm happy to report that this morning, she was found walking along a road in Yokohama.
Hey, kiddo. You remember back then?
Back when?
You were in fifth grade and something like this happened in the neighborhood.
Do you remember that?
It's okay if you don't. Us parents got together and decided the best thing was to try to get you kids to forget about it.
You didn't know, but your life was in danger.
When I was in fifth grade, a kidnapping?
I remember. Two classmates of mine went missing.
I was a shy kid. And then I met this local guy, Yuki. He'd play with me.
Yuki wasn't his real name, but I called him that. He'd always say, have courage.
I bet I know what the most popular kid in your class is like.
Huh?
For starters, I bet he's cheerful and good at sports. He ain't afraid to speak up for himself.
And he can be a goofball too, but not when it comes to something he's super into.
Whoa.
No biggie. Popular folks are always like that.
Y-you could be like that too if you want to.
Just follow that kid's lead. And don't be shy.
Cause if you have courage, you can do anything.
Six months after my classmates disappeared, Jun Shiratori was arrested for kidnapping and murder.
It was Yuki.
Why'd you have to buy so much?
You got those okay?
I'm gonna make enough curry to last you a whole week.
Oh, honey. See, that's why I told you not to run.
I told you not to run. Let's go and get you another one.
Hey, you okay back there?
Yeah.
You got those okay?
I'm gonna make enough curry to last you a whole week.
Another revival.
Oh, honey. See, that's why I told you not to run. Let's go and get you another one.
Crap. Where is it? Come on, man. Find it. Find it.
Find it. Find it.
Hey, Mom. You notice anything weird?
Like what?
Look around. Don't you feel like something's off here?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Wait. Come to think of it, you said the same thing when you were a little kid, too.
Did I?
Yeah. Remember the fire?
Oh!
Was that guy looking at me?
Nothing happened.
Hey, Fujinuma!
Over here!
She's your mom? She looked so young, I thought she was your sister.
Do you believe in witches?
I do now.
Is she mad at you or something?
No.
Um...Irie?
Would you like to come over and have some curry with us?
Yes, ma'am! I totally would!
Thank you for the invite! I'll even help you make it!
Seriously?
No way! You draw manga?
Does that shock you?
Not at all. If it's on Wicketanica, it must be true.
You looked me up?
Of course. Why not?
Okay, guys. Dig in.
Why?
Cause I don't want you to.
This smells yummy!
Wow! It is yummy!
You did help. You know, for someone so young, you really know your way around a curry.
So how long have you guys been dating?
Oh no, it's not like that.
He's more like a friend.
A friend I have tons of respect for.
What? Too spicy for you?
No. It's great.
It was super nice meeting you.
I can give you a lift to the station.
It's already so late. You can spend the night if you want.
No, she can't, Mom. She's in high school.
Thanks for having me over. And for the ride, Satoru.
No worries. Just keep an eye out for cops, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Welcome home.
Let's get something straight, Mom.
She's not a potential wife for me. She's my co-worker.
Oh, please. Don't be so dense.
You hurt her. She respects you.
You totally have a shot with her.
God, she was just being polite.
Don't go blowing a compliment out of proportion.
I'm not. She doesn't seem like the type who'd say that unless you meant it.
Huh?
Oh, by the way, your landlady came over asking about the rent.
Great.
Satoru, about this afternoon.
What?
In the market's parking lot.
Yeah? What's up? What about it?
I think you might have stopped a kid from getting snatched.
You're kidding!
You're right. I am kidding.
I remember.
She was a classmate of mine 18 years ago. She was one of the kidnapper's victims.
Kayo Hinazuki.
We weren't friends or anything, but I'd always see her alone at the park.
That night at the park was the last time I saw Kayo.
No, you don't get it! I could have saved her!
If I'd have asked her to walk home with me, she'd still be alive!
Back then, all I wanted was to forget how guilty I felt.
I know my mom did everything she could to erase it from my memory.
Readers want to see what makes an artist tick.
You gotta dig deep down into yourself. That's what art's all about.
His car had rental plates. He was gonna kidnap her for sure.
Did he change his mind cause I saw him?
He turned away like he was hiding his face.
He definitely knew me.
And I know I've seen those eyes somewhere.
But on who?
And where?
When?
That's it!
I remember now.
Oh my god.
Shiratori's not the killer after all.
Hey, it's Sachiko.
Yeah, it's been a while.
The statute of limitations on those murders ran out a while ago.
And god knows how many kids he must have killed over the past 18 years.
The case is anything but closed.
I have to talk to Satoru.
The time's come to set him straight on what happened back then.
Satoru?
I was right.
Have to call Satoru.
Tell him to stay away.
Tell him sorry.
I know I could have saved Kaio's life.
Yuki didn't kill her.
I know I didn't.
He didn't do it, Mom!
He didn't!
I should have believed you back then.
The police didn't.
But...
I should have.
I'm sorry.
Satoru.
I'm heading home now.
See y'all tomorrow.
Nice hustle today!
See you tomorrow!
See ya!
Night!
Before you go...
Hmm?
I bet I can guess what you had for breakfast today.
What?
Curry!
You're right.
Yes!
Obviously.
Mom made a ton of it.
Oh, hey!
Could you ask your mom to cook some more of her curry?
I've never tasted anything so amazing.
Yeah, I'll let her know.
Later.
Huh?
What a slob!
Geez.
What a slob.
Hey, Mom. This isn't Hokkaido. It's the city.
You can't just leave the door open like...
Hey. Mom?
Come on, cut it out. This isn't funny.
Come on, say something. Get up.
Mom!
I brought back your dish, Satoru. Your mom's curry was...
No, wait!
There was blood all over his hands.
Are you Satoru Fujinuma?
What the hell?
No. It wasn't me.
I didn't do it. I didn't kill her!
I didn't kill her!
Hey, don't even...
Wait. Is this revival?
But...
Where did I end up?
I've seen this before, but...
When?
Hurry up, Satoru! You're gonna be late!
I... I know that kid.
When is this?
What is this?
Nineteen...
Eighty-eight?
The End
See you next time.
Yeah.